http://www.toyota.co.uk/footer/cookie-policy-settings

Motability
What is the Motability scheme?
Book a test drive
Toyota (GB) PLC and Toyota Financial Services (UK) PLC ('we') are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. On this page we describe how we may use any personal data that you supply to us when you visit this website and the Toyota 'My Finance' mobile app. You can amend your consent to this at any time.
What is a cookie?
Why do we collect cookies?
See what types of cookies we use
Manage your cookies
What is a cookie?
A cookie is a small piece of data sent from our webpage and stored in your web browser, mobile phone, or other device while you are using our website. It helps the page recognise your device the next time you visit, provides you with access to certain functions, and understands your website journey. Cookies are very common web technology - most websites use cookies.
You can read more about the different types of cookies that we use on this website on this
page.
Why do we collect cookies?
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users on our website. This helps us to provide you with a better experience when you browse our website and also allows us to make improvements to our site.
You can read more about the different types of cookies that we use on this website on this
page.
However, if you want to find out more on how to disable cookies go to 'Manage my cookies' section
here.
See what types of cookies we use
There are four different types of cookies, based on their function and purpose:
1. Strictly Necessary cookies
Cookies that are essential, also known as 'strictly necessary' cookies, enable features without which you would not be able to use the website as intended.
Cookie Provider
Cookie Name
Purpose
Amazon web service
AWSELB
AWSALBAWSELBCORS
This helps to automatically distribute web traffic to different servers as visitor numbers change.
Celebrus
tgbc*
Stores visitors' cookie consent choices and used for auditing purposes.
Inscapsula
incap_*nlbi_*visid_incap_*express:sess*express:sess.sig*
Used to improve website speed and security.
Dynatrace
dt*rx*
Helps us to track broken functionality and maintain security.
Laravel
laravel_session
Cookie used to identify a session instance for the user.
TME
TmeEPrivacy
Stores users' cookie consent choices to manage cookie preferences.
2. Performance cookies
These cookies collect information about how visitors use toyota.co.uk for instance which pages visitors go to most often. These cookies don't collect information that identifies a visitor. It is only used to improve how our website works.
Cookie Provider
Cookie Name
Purpose
Content Square
Privacy policy
_ga
_cs_id
_cs_s
_cs_vars
_cs_ex
_cs_c
_cs_output
These cookies differentiate between different users of the website and see what pages they are visiting.
It enables Toyota to identify and understand any issues in your journey through our website as a customer. The data we collect is centred around improving the experience for our customers. Having this information helps Toyota
to identify the sections, functionality and products on the website that are working well and are useful to our customers, as well as those that aren't working so well, so we can
improve your experience. ContentSquare is a solution which aggregates usage and frequency data to improve user experience.
Statistics created are anonymous.
Pingdom
Privacy policy
_ga sid,
sst,
sis,
rv,
pa_enabled,
This cookie helps us to understand the load speeds on our site and to make sure everything is working.
The random session ID means it is anonymous.
New Relic
Privacy policy
JSESSIONID
Provides a platform for monitoring the performance of web and mobile applications.
Google Analytics
Privacy policy
_ga
_gid
_gat
Google Analytics helps us understand how our visitors get to our website, the number of people that visit our site, and how they navigate their way around the site once they're there. We can use this information to improve our visitors' user experience.
Google OptimisePrivacy policy
__utmx
__utmxx
Google Optimise uses cookies to understand, improve, develop and research products, features and services, to collect usage, viewing, logs, and technical information about your visit, and to create logs and record when users access our site.
These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. These cookies are collected and aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.
Usabilla
Privacy policy
usbls
This cookie will be used to track whether users are new or returning visitors and to then show the campaign to the right users.
Cloudflare__cfduidThis cookie is used to verify users with a shared IP address and applies security settings to reduce spam attacks.
cf_bmAdded by Cloudflare when traffic is suspected to be spam.
cf_ob_info & cf_use_obThese may be set to serve cached data to website visitors.
Feefofeefo.snippets-flag.{uuid}These combined ensure the correct functionality and interactions with the Feefo Owner Reviews
feefo.translationsLocal storage
feefo.translationsUpdatedAtLocal storage
feefo.{slug}.helpful_uuidLocal storage
feefo.{slug}.problem_uuidLocal storage
feefotestLocal storage
feefoUserIdUsed for anonymised tracking.
helpful_uuidUsed for rating media & feedbacks as helpful.
problem_uuidUsed for identifying problems with media.
3. Functional Cookies
These cookies enable a website to save information which has already been entered (such as user names, language choices, and your location), so that it can offer you improved and more personalised functions. Functional cookies are also used to enable features you request such as playing videos. These cookies collect anonymous information and cannot track your movements on other websites.
Cookie Provider
Cookie Name
Purpose
Twitter
Privacy policy
lang
This functionality is used to recognise language preferences.
Bold360 by LogMeIn
Privacy policy
_bcvm_vid_XXXXXX
_bcvm_vrid_XXXXXX
bc_pv_end
bc-visit-id
bc-visitor-id
_bc-curl
_url-cid
_bc_aa*
_reboot-cid
bc.visitor_token,
u,
35EBBB4,
Spt,
bc.visitor_token,
nanorep.float.conversational
.product_demo.kb904641352
Stores a unique, anonymous identifier (VisitorID) to allow Bold360 to recognize the website user during current and subsequent visits to the website. Also used to enable the functionality of online live chat and collect non-personally identifiable information related to the use of online chat bot. We can use this information to improve our visitors' user experience.
Ignition One
Privacy policy
evo5_TOYOTA
evo5_TOYOTA_popin
Used to measure website engagement and to trigger a pop up form for test drive, quote and brochure requests.
Codeweavers
_CWTC
Enables the functionality of the on-site finance calculator.
4. Advertising Cookies
These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. We also use them to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of our digital advertising campaigns. They are placed by third party advertising networks on our behalf and with Toyotaís permission. They remember that you have visited Toyota.co.uk and this is shared with other organisations such as media owners.
Cookie Provider
Cookie Name
Purpose
Facebook
Privacy policy
datrc fr
lu
Uses a unique ID to make sure that any advertising you see from us on Facebook, is relevant and personalised. To prevent this from happening, you will need to review your Facebook adverting preferences in your Facebook profile settings.
Youtube
Privacy policy
SID
HSID
Demographics
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
PREF
APISID
SSID
YSC
LOGIN_INFO
SAPISID
Uses a unique ID to make sure that any advertising you see from us on You Tube is relevant and personalised.
LinkedIn
Privacy policy
leo_auth_token
lidc
bcookie
__utma
__utmv
__utmz
bscookie
__qca
visit
Uses a unique ID to make sure that any advertising you see from us on LinkedIn is relevant and personalised.
Twitter
auth_token
twll
__utmz
secure_session
guest_id
__utma
personalization_id
remember_checked
remember_checked_on
Uses a unique ID to make sure that any advertising you see from us on Twitter is relevant and personalised.
Google
_ga
_gid
_gid
_gat
_ga
APISID
SSID
APISID
Uses a unique ID to make sure that any advertising you see from us on Google Sites is relevant and personalised.
[m]]PLATFORM (mookie1.com)
Privacy policy
id
mdata
syncdata_ <PARTNER >
Used to measure the performance of our digital advertising so we can ensure it is more relevant and personalised.
AppNexus
Privacy policy
anj
sess
uuid2
Used for serving relevant and personalised advertising to you after you have visited our site and limit the number of times you see an ad.
DoubleClick by Google
Privacy policy
id
Used to measure performance from our digital advertising activity so we can target our advertising more effectively and make sure it is more relevant.
Xaxis (Adswizz)
pixelg.adswizz.com
Used for serving relevant advertising to you after you have visited our site, and providing reporting on the effectiveness of the advertising.
Netmining
netmng
Uses a unique ID to measure activity across the site and help us to improve the site.
Double click floodlight
doubleclick.net
Used to measure performance from our digital advertising activity so we can target our advertising more effectively and make it more relevant to you.
Facebook connect
_fbq
Uses a unique ID to make sure that any advertising you see from us on Facebook, is relevant and personalised
GA audiences
_ga, _gid
Uses a unique ID to make sure that any advertising you see from us on Google Sites is relevant and personalised and limit the number of times you see an advertisement
Linked in analytics
ads.linkedin.com
linkedin.com
Uses a unique ID to measure activity across the Linked in site and limit the number of times you see our advertising
Twitter Analytics and Conversion
_twq
This pixel is used to generate audiences within Twitter and track media performance so that you see advertising that is relevant and interesting
Adform
adform.net
Used for providing reporting on the effectiveness of the advertising and limit the number of times you see an advertisement
Captify
secure.adnxs.com/px?id=1061842
Used for providing reporting on the effectiveness of the advertising and limit the number of times you see an advertisement
Manage your cookies
Cookies on Toyota Website
There are four different types of cookies, based on their function and purpose:
Strictly necessary
Cookies that are essential, also known as 'strictly necessary' cookies, enable features without which you would not be able to use the website as intended.
Performance
These cookies help us to understand how you use our website so that we can improve it and test new ideas.
Functional
These cookies help us to personalise your visit, by remembering your preferences and settings, such as pages you have visited and cars you have explored.
Advertising
These are used to tailor our off-site advertising and help to make our advertising and content more relevant and personalised to you.
Save
You can find more information about Cookies at:
www.allaboutcookies.org and www.youronlinechoices.eu
Build your car
Find your dealer
Brochures & price lists
Quick Finance Calculator
Book a test drive
Privacy Policy
Legal
Book a test drive
© Toyota (GB) PLC is a company registered in England and Wales with registered company number 0916634 with its registered office at Great Burgh, Burgh Heath, Epsom, Surrey, KT18 5UX. Toyota (GB) PLC is a member of the Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders.Toyota Financial Services (UK) PLC. Registered Office: Great Burgh, Burgh Heath, Epsom, Surrey, KT18 5UZ. Registered in England with Number 02299961. Authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority.
